Guide to the Franz R. and Kathryn M. Stenzel Research Files on Western American Art
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Other Research and Writings Files, 1936-1983; Series VI; 1.05; (3 boxes)
  Series VI, Other Research and Writings Files, is
  organized into two subseries: Research Files and
  Writings. The Research Files are arranged by Subject
  Files, Writings by Others, Printed Material, Slides and
  Photographs and Other Papers.
  - RESEARCH FILES
    - Subject Files
      - "Bancroft Oregon Notes", n.d. (Box 36, Folder 628)
      - [Darley] "Indian Captive" [painting question], 1962, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 629)
      - "Editorial Form" [information on conducting and citing research], 1960-77, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 630)
      - "Honeyman Collection Inventory, Bancroft Library, 1965", n.d. (Box 36, Folder 631)
      - "Institution" [information on libraries and museums], 1958-67, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 632-634)
      - National Academy of Design - notes on exhibitions, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 635)
      - "Tacoma Portland Lecture" [materials on Remington and Russell], 1965, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 636)
        Includes information on loan of
        Remington and Russell materials to
        Allied Arts Center, Tacoma
      - "University Oregon" [survey forms for three paintings in private hands] (Box 36, Folder 637)
      - "Vital Statistics", 1962-74, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 638)
      - "Webber. Spokane Library" [appraisal of two drawings by Webber], 1968 (Box 36, Folder 639)
    - Printed Material
      - Exhibition Catalogs
        - Bohemian Club. Copies of catalogs dated 1925-1947, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 640)
        - Island Arts' Club of Victoria, B.C. Exhibition catalogs, 1910-1941. Copies (Box 36, Folder 641-643)
        - Vancouver Art Gallery. Copies of catalogs dated 1932-1953, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 644-646)
        - Washington Writers and Pacific Coast Painters and Sculptors, 1936 (Box 37, Folder 647)
      - Other Printed Material
        - Art Directory of California, 1932, from California Arts & Crafts. Photocopy, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 648)
        - Harold G. Davidson art catalogs, 1965-76 (Box 37, Folder 649)
        - Montana Gallery - Book Shoppe catalogs, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 650)
        - Bookseller and art dealer catalogs, 1964, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 651)
        - "Governors of Oregon" column from The Oregonian by George S. Turnbull, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 652)
        - Miscellaneous clippings and newsletters, 1959-83, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 653)
        - Miscellaneous printed material, 1965-73, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 654)
    - Slides and Photographs
      - Slides of Western Art, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 655-658)
        Includes slides of Cleveland Rockwell
        art from the Oregon Historical
        Society, and several slides portraying
        the Stenzels
      - Miscellaneous copy photographs, negatives and reproductions, 1967, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 659)
        Includes copy photograph of Theodore
        Roosevelt [?] on horseback by
        photographer Stinson of Cheyenne,
        and two copy photographs of John
        McLoughlin [?]
    - Other Papers
      - Cornwell, Luther B. Letter written during the Civil War. Holograph copy (Box 38, Folder 660)
      - Letter to A. B. Frothingham from an unidentified artist, who writes a short autobiographical sketch. Typescript copy, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 661)
        Letter dated Hudson, N.Y., 1874 Nov 6
      - Gibbs, George and Edmund A. Starling. "Sketch of the Willamette Valley, showing the purchases and reservations made by the Board of Commissioners appointed to treat with the Indians of Oregon April and May, 1831." Copy
      - Parks, George A. Early Exploratory Routes Alaska. Copy, n.d.
      - Stansbury, M. H. Map of the United States Territory of Oregon West of the Rocky Mountains. Washington, 1838. Copy, n.d.
      - Thompson, David. "Three Tetons Strip - Map 1824. British Museum." Colored copy (Box 38, Folder 662)
  - WRITINGS
    - Writings by Stenzel
      - Untitled short paper on art of the Oregon Country. Typescript, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 663)
      - Notes on "Concepts of Analysis and Interpretation of Art Objects." Typescript (Box 38, Folder 664)
      - "Forgeries, Duplications and Copies." Typescript (Box 38, Folder 665)
      - "Washington Early Communities." Typescript carbon biographical sketches of seven artists, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 666)
        Stored also in: Correspondence for
        Washington Historical Society
      - Western History Association lecture on Northwest Art. Typescript carbon, corrected, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 667)
      - Notes, possibly by Stenzel, on four artists and an artwork by each. Typescript carbon (Box 38, Folder 668)
      - Miscellaneous notes, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 669)
    - Writings by Others
      - Douglas Cole and Maria Tippett on British Columbia artists, particularly Emily Carr and Paul Rand. Copies, 1977 (Box 38, Folder 670)
        Accompanied by letter from Douglas
        Cole
      - Comstock, Sophia P. "Painters of Northern California. Part I. Read before the Kingsley Art Club, Sacramento, March 15th, 1909." Copy, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 671)
      - Meuli, Karl. "Peter Rindisbacher the Indian Painter from the Emmenthal." Typescript, corrected (Box 38, Folder 672)
      - "Diary of Theodore Wygant." Typescript transcript of gold rush diary, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 673)
      - Diary of a soldier on Sibley's Expedition against the Sioux in 1863. Typescript transcript, corrected, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 674)
      - Wiley, W. H. "As You Like It." Typescript poem, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 674a)
- Correspondence, 1941-1986; Series VII; 5.67; (14 boxes)
  Series VII, Correspondence, consists primarily of
  typescript carbons of Franz Stenzel's outgoing
  correspondence. Letters from correspondents not listed
  individually may be found in "letter" general folders.
  - "A" general, 1959-75, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 675-679)
  - Abajian, James de T., 1973 (Box 39, Folder 680)
    See also: California Historical Society, box 41, folders 806-807
  - Achey, John, 1963-64 (Box 39, Folder 681)
  - Adams, Virginia (Mrs. Ansel), 1960 (Box 39, Folder 682)
  - Adams, Earl, 1967-73 (Box 39, Folder 683)
  - Adams, Philip, 1962-66 (Box 39, Folder 684)
  - Addison Gallery of American Art, 1959-64 (Box 39, Folder 685)
  - Adelphi Book Shop, 1962-65 (Box 39, Folder 686)
  - Adirondack Museum, 1963-64 (Box 39, Folder 687)
  - Agghazy, Leslie, 1964-72 (Box 39, Folder 688)
  - Alaska State Museum, 1965-73 (Box 39, Folder 689)
  - Alcorn, Gordon, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 690)
  - Alford, Edith, 1959-64 (Box 39, Folder 691)
    See also: Lute Pease, box 48, folder 1245
  - Allen, Edward, 1963 (Box 39, Folder 692)
  - Allen, Nat, 1966 (Box 39, Folder 693)
  - Allied Arts of Tacoma, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 694)
  - American Book Collector, 1964-66 (Box 39, Folder 695)
  - American Federation of Arts, 1959-75 (Box 39, Folder 696)
  - American Heritage Publishing Co., Inc., 1963-66 (Box 39, Folder 697)
  - American Institute of Architects, 1963-64 (Box 39, Folder 698)
  - American Museum of Natural History, 1963-66 (Box 39, Folder 699)
  - American Watercolor Society, 1963 (Box 39, Folder 700)
  - Amherst College, 1964-73 (Box 39, Folder 701)
  - Amick, Robert, 1961-64 (Box 39, Folder 702)
  - Ammon, Charles; Ammon, Violet, 1963-64 (Box 39, Folder 703)
  - Amon Carter Museum, 1961-83, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 704-712)
  - Appling, Howell, 1959-63 (Box 39, Folder 713)
  - Archives of American Art, 1963-76 (Box 39, Folder 714)
  - Argosy Gallery, 1961-76 (Box 39, Folder 715)
  - Art Gallery of Greater Victoria, 1963-64 (Box 39, Folder 716)
  - Arthur H. Clark Company, 1963-67 (Box 39, Folder 717)
  - Atwater, Irving, Mr. and Mrs., 1964-65 (Box 39, Folder 718)
  - Ayars, Glen, Mrs., 1959-60 (Box 39, Folder 719)
  - "B" general, 1959-79, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 720-731)
  - Back, Joseph, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 732)
  - Bagglemann, Ted, 1962 (Box 40, Folder 733)
  - Baillargeon, John, 1963-64 (Box 40, Folder 734)
  - Baird, Joseph Armstrong, 1963-75 (Box 40, Folder 735-736)
  - Bamford, Hal, 1963-64 (Box 40, Folder 737)
  - Bancroft Library, 1962-76, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 738-739)
  - Banghart, Donna, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 740)
  - Banghart, Edith, 1963-64 (Box 40, Folder 741)
  - Bank of California, 1967 (Box 40, Folder 742)
  - Barrette, Leonore, 1962-64 (Box 40, Folder 743)
  - Barnes, Gordon, 1963-64 (Box 40, Folder 744)
  - Barry, J. Neilson, 1958 (Box 40, Folder 745)
  - Barry, T. D., 1962-63 (Box 40, Folder 746)
  - Bartlett, Elizabeth, 1959-66 (Box 40, Folder 747)
  - Baylor, Allen O., 1972 (Box 40, Folder 748)
  - Beaver Magazine, 1962-73 (Box 40, Folder 749)
  - Becker, Roland F., 1963-64 (Box 40, Folder 750)
  - Beecher, Henry Ward, Mrs., 1958-62 (Box 40, Folder 751)
  - Beery, Noah, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 752)
  - Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library, 1962-75 (Box 40, Folder 753-754)
  - Belluschi, Pietro, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 755)
  - Benson, Evelyn, 1961 Nov (Box 40, Folder 756)
  - Berenson, Bernard, 1963, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 757)
  - Berry-Hill Galleries, 1962-71, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 758)
  - Bertsche, William H.
    See: C.M. Russell Museum, box 41, folders 798-801
  - Best, Nelson L., 1960-77 (Box 40, Folder 759)
  - Best, Stella, 1964, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 760)
  - Beuf, Carlo, 1962-67 (Box 40, Folder 761)
  - Bichsel, Lettie J., 1959-61 (Box 40, Folder 762)
  - Binford, Thomas, Mrs., 1965-67 (Box 40, Folder 763)
  - Bishop, Marcia, 1968 May (Box 40, Folder 764)
  - Bloomington-Normal Art Association, 1962 (Box 40, Folder 765)
  - Blumenschein, Helen G., 1963 (Box 40, Folder 766)
  - Boggs, Mae Helene Bacon, 1959 (Box 40, Folder 767)
  - Bolton, John H., 1963-64 (Box 40, Folder 768)
  - Borglum, George, 1963 Mar 8 (Box 40, Folder 769)
  - Borglum, Lincoln, 1963-65 (Box 40, Folder 770)
  - Borglum, Mary, 1962 Nov 26 (Box 40, Folder 771)
  - Boston Public Library, 1963-65 (Box 40, Folder 772)
  - Bowden, John, 1959-62 (Box 40, Folder 773)
  - Bowditch, Nancy, 1963-74 (Box 40, Folder 774)
  - Brookgreen Gardens, 1963-65 (Box 40, Folder 775)
  - Brooklyn Museum, 1962-65 (Box 40, Folder 776)
  - Brown and Bigelow, 1962-63 (Box 40, Folder 777)
  - Browne, Evelyn, 1963-65 (Box 40, Folder 778)
  - Browne, Spencer, Mrs., 1963-65 (Box 40, Folder 779)
  - Bruce's Books, 1961-66 (Box 40, Folder 780)
  - Bryson, B. J., 1966 Nov (Box 40, Folder 781)
  - Buckley, W. W., Mrs., 1965-66 (Box 40, Folder 782)
  - Buff's Galleries, 1966 May (Box 40, Folder 783)
  - Burford, Ida, 1963, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 784)
  - Butler, Russell, 1963-65 (Box 40, Folder 785)
  - Butler Institute of American Art, 1960-65 (Box 40, Folder 786)
  - "C" general, 1959-79, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 787-796)
  - C. F. Braun & Co., 1964-65 (Box 41, Folder 797)
  - C.M. Russell Museum, 1959-75, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 798-801)
  - Cahill, Arthur, 1963-64 (Box 41, Folder 802)
  - Calgary Public Library, 1964-65 (Box 41, Folder 803)
  - California Department of Public Health, 1962-73 (Box 41, Folder 804-805)
  - California Historical Society, 1959-73, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 806-807)
    See also: Abajian, James de T., box 39, folder 680; Baird, Joseph Armstrong, box 40, folders 735-736; Shumate, Albert, box 49, folders 1361
  - California State Library, 1959-64 (Box 41, Folder 808-809)
  - Campbell, Forest, 1960-63 (Box 41, Folder 810)
  - Campbell, J. Allan, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 811)
  - Canadian Pacific Railroad, 1962-64 (Box 41, Folder 812)
  - Card, Helen, 1963-67 (Box 41, Folder 813)
  - Carothers, Ruth, 1963-65 (Box 41, Folder 814)
  - Cartmell, Bernard, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 815)
  - Caughell, C. G., 1959 (Box 41, Folder 816)
  - Caughey, A. Rollin, 1960-62 (Box 41, Folder 817)
  - Caxton Printers, 1963-64 (Box 41, Folder 818)
  - Center, Bill, 1965-66 (Box 41, Folder 819)
  - Chapellier Gallery, 1961-66, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 820)
  - Charles, Kate, 1962-64 (Box 41, Folder 821)
  - Charman, Elbert B., 1958-59 (Box 41, Folder 822)
  - Cheyenne Centennial Celebration Committee, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 823)
  - Chicago Historical Society, 1963 (Box 41, Folder 824)
  - Chicago Public Library, 1963-65 (Box 41, Folder 825)
  - Childs Gallery, 1957-62 (Box 41, Folder 826)
  - Christlieb, J. M., 1959-62 (Box 41, Folder 827)
  - Chuinard, E. G., 1966-74 (Box 41, Folder 828)
  - Cincinnati Art Museum, 1963-67 (Box 41, Folder 829)
  - City Art Museum of St. Louis, 1958-59 (Box 41, Folder 830)
  - Clark, Irving, 1960-71, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 831)
  - Cleveland Museum of Art, 1962-75 (Box 41, Folder 832)
  - Cobham, George H., 1963-66 (Box 41, Folder 833)
  - Cole, Douglas, 1972-77 (Box 41, Folder 834)
  - Cole, J. Fred, 1960 Mar (Box 41, Folder 835)
  - Colorado School of Mines, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 836)
  - Columbia River Maritime Museum, 1962-72, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 837)
  - Cooke, Gaylord K., 1964 (Box 41, Folder 838)
  - Cooney, Fanny, 1965 Feb (Box 41, Folder 839)
  - Corbett, Fred, Mrs., 1964-65 (Box 41, Folder 840)
  - Corcoran Gallery of Art, 1963-65 (Box 41, Folder 841)
  - Coulter, James V., 1963-67 (Box 41, Folder 842)
  - Cowan, John, 1958-64 (Box 41, Folder 843)
  - Cowdrey, Mary Bartlett, 1961-74 (Box 41, Folder 844)
  - Craig, Ethel, 1962-63 (Box 41, Folder 845)
  - Cram, Leo D., 1963-64 (Box 41, Folder 846)
  - Creden, Gwendolyn, 1962 (Box 41, Folder 847)
  - Creese, Walter, 1964-65 (Box 41, Folder 848)
  - Crestmoor Galleries, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 849)
  - Cutler, O. S., Mrs., 1960-65 (Box 41, Folder 850)
  - Cutter, Donald, 1961-62 (Box 41, Folder 851)
  - "D" general, 1957-75, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 852-856)
  - Dahl, Ottar M., 1960-73, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 857-858)
  - Dartnell, Radford, Mrs., 1959-63 (Box 42, Folder 859)
  - Davidson, Harold, 1970-71 (Box 42, Folder 860)
  - Davies, A. Mervyn, Mrs., 1963-67 (Box 42, Folder 861)
  - Davis, Joe, 1963 Oct (Box 42, Folder 862)
  - Davis, Walter, 1960-63, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 863)
  - Dawson's Book Shop, 1960-75 (Box 42, Folder 864)
  - De Beaumont, Edmond, 1961-67 (Box 42, Folder 865)
  - De Camp, Renan, Mrs., 1963 (Box 42, Folder 866)
  - Delaware Art Museum, 1977 Aug 13 (Box 42, Folder 867)
  - DeNeffe, Frederick, 1962-64 (Box 42, Folder 868)
  - Denver Art Museum, 1960-72 (Box 42, Folder 869)
  - Denver Public Library, 1959-72 (Box 42, Folder 870)
  - Desert-Southwest Art Gallery, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 871)
  - Detroit Institute of Arts, 1960-74 (Box 42, Folder 872)
  - DeWitt, O. K., Mr. and Mrs., 1960-62 (Box 42, Folder 873)
  - DeYoung Museum, 1964 (Box 42, Folder 874)
  - District of Columbia Department of Public Health, 1964-75 (Box 42, Folder 875)
  - District of Columbia Public Library, 1963-66 (Box 42, Folder 876)
  - Dixon, Ruth, 1963-77, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 877-880)
  - Dora Hood's Book Room, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 881)
  - Dow, Robert, 1972-75 (Box 42, Folder 882)
  - Doyle, Eileen, 1964 Dec 14 (Box 42, Folder 883)
  - Driscoll, Emily, 1960-76 (Box 42, Folder 884)
  - Drury, Clifford M., 1959-72 (Box 42, Folder 885)
  - Ducker, Ada, 1963-64 (Box 42, Folder 886)
  - Duckett, Kenneth, 1958-63, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 887)
    See also: Oregon Historical Society, box 47, folders 1223-1224
  - Duryee, Marjorie, 1964 (Box 42, Folder 888)
  - Dykes, Jeff, 1964-74 (Box 42, Folder 889)
  - "E" general, 1959-75 (Box 42, Folder 890-892)
  - Eastern Washington State Historical Society, 1961-73 (Box 42, Folder 893-896)
  - Edgett, Beverly, 1959-63 (Box 42, Folder 897)
  - Edmonton Art Gallery, 1964-67 (Box 42, Folder 898)
  - Edmund Scientific Company, 1962 (Box 42, Folder 899)
  - Edward Eberstadt & Sons, 1956-65 (Box 42, Folder 900)
  - Edwards, David S., 1964-72, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 901)
  - Eggenhofer, Nick, 1964 (Box 42, Folder 902)
  - Ellis, Frances B., 1959-64 (Box 42, Folder 903)
  - Ellis, Grace, 1963 (Box 42, Folder 904)
  - Elmberg, Martin O., Mrs., 1966-67 (Box 42, Folder 905)
  - Elwell, Kathryn, 1964-65 (Box 42, Folder 906)
  - Emeline Fairbanks Memorial Library, 1964 (Box 42, Folder 907)
  - Eskridge, Helen; Eskridge, Robert, 1962-65 (Box 42, Folder 908)
  - Eubank, Charles, 1967 Jan (Box 43, Folder 909)
  - Evans, William H., 1959-62 (Box 43, Folder 910)
  - Ewers, John C., 1963-78, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 911)
    See also: United States National Museum, box 50, folders 1423-1424
  - "F" general, 1958-76 (Box 43, Folder 912-915)
  - Faddis, George, 1966-75 (Box 43, Folder 916)
  - Fairbanks, Avard, 1963-64 (Box 43, Folder 917)
  - Fairfield Antique Gallery, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 918)
  - Farnsworth, Henry S., 1963-66 (Box 43, Folder 919)
  - Farrington, Albert; Farrington, Jane, 1961-68 (Box 43, Folder 920)
  - Faudé, C. Fredrick, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 921)
  - Fay, Jean Bradford, 1964-65 (Box 43, Folder 922)
  - Ferbraché, Lewis, 1960-72, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 923-925)
    See also: Oakland Museum, box 47, folders 1213-1214
  - Ferguson, Mary Elrod, 1963 (Box 43, Folder 926)
  - Fery, Carl, 1960-64 (Box 43, Folder 927)
  - Fery, Lucienne, 1961-63 (Box 43, Folder 928)
  - Fetherolf, Grace, 1964-65 (Box 43, Folder 929)
  - Fields, Lillian S., 1963-65 (Box 43, Folder 930)
  - Fife, Esther, 1964 (Box 43, Folder 931)
  - Fine Arts Gallery, 1965, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 932)
  - Fitch, Richard, 1973-74 (Box 43, Folder 933)
  - Flagstaff Public Library, 1963-64 (Box 43, Folder 934)
  - Flick, Belton J., 1967-69 (Box 43, Folder 935)
  - Florida State Museum, 1965 Sep (Box 43, Folder 936)
  - Forrest, James
    See: Museum of New Mexico, box 46, folders 1182-1185; Thomas Gilcrease Foundation, box 50, folders 1405-1406
  - Fort Vancouver Historical Society, 1962-69 (Box 43, Folder 937)
  - Fort Worth Art Center, 1959-65 (Box 43, Folder 938)
  - Fragley, Albert, 1962-73 (Box 43, Folder 939-941)
  - Fraser, Laura G., 1963 (Box 43, Folder 942)
  - Free Library of Philadelphia, 1962-65 (Box 43, Folder 943)
  - Free Public Library, New Bedford, 1963-66 (Box 43, Folder 944)
  - Frick Art Reference Library, 1954-62 (Box 43, Folder 945)
  - Frost, Ruby, 1959-63 (Box 43, Folder 946)
  - Furlong, Charles Wellington, 1964-66 (Box 43, Folder 947)
  - "G" general, 1959-86, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 948-953)
  - G. K. Hall and Company, 1964 (Box 43, Folder 954)
  - Gaffken, William, 1963-65 (Box 43, Folder 955)
  - Gale, William E., 1959-74 (Box 43, Folder 956)
  - Galka and Roman Fine Paintings, 1963 (Box 43, Folder 957)
  - Gallery West, 1968-72, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 958)
  - Gannon, William, 1963-65 (Box 43, Folder 959)
  - Ganz, Julian; Ganz, Jo Ann, 1975, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 960)
  - Garcia, Ellis, Mrs., 1962 (Box 43, Folder 961)
  - Gegoux, F. G., Mrs., 1967-73 (Box 43, Folder 962)
  - Gegoux, Victor, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 963)
  - General Mills, Inc., 1962 (Box 43, Folder 964)
  - George, Clarence W., Mrs., 1960-63 (Box 43, Folder 965)
  - Gerald Peters Gallery, 1984-86 (Box 43, Folder 965a)
  - Gernon, John, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 966)
  - Gibson, Glenn M., 1975 (Box 43, Folder 967)
  - Giessel, Fred M., 1962-72, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 968)
  - Gifford, James, 1965-66 (Box 43, Folder 969)
  - Gifford, Sanford, Mrs., 1963 (Box 43, Folder 970)
  - Gilbreath Chemical Company, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 971)
  - Gleason, Joe Duncan, Mrs., 1967-68 (Box 43, Folder 972)
  - Glenbow-Alberta Institute, 1961-75, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 973-974)
  - Glover, A. Lawrence, 1964-65 (Box 43, Folder 975)
  - Gonzaga University, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 976)
  - Goodall, Mary, 1959 (Box 43, Folder 977)
  - Goodrich, Charles, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 978)
  - Goodspeed's Book Shop, 1959-74 (Box 44, Folder 979)
  - Goodwin, Theodore R., 1963-64 (Box 44, Folder 980)
  - Gordon, Charles S., 1962-63 (Box 44, Folder 981)
  - Gould, Dorothy, 1959-66 (Box 44, Folder 982)
  - Grand Central Art Galleries, 1963-65 (Box 44, Folder 983)
  - Granger, Bruce Ingham, 1963-64 (Box 44, Folder 984)
  - Graves, Eleanor, 1961-62 (Box 44, Folder 985)
  - Great Northern Railway, 1960-62 (Box 44, Folder 986)
  - Groll, Gabrielle P., 1964-65 (Box 44, Folder 987)
  - Grubar, Francis S., 1966-80 (Box 44, Folder 988)
  - Gustin, Paul, 1963-64 (Box 44, Folder 989)
  - "H" general, 1958-76, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 990-999)
  - H.P. Kraus, 1965 Oct (Box 44, Folder 1000)
  - Hager, Orval O., 1968 (Box 44, Folder 1001)
  - Hale, Mary V., 1960-63 (Box 44, Folder 1002)
  - Hall, Bob, 1962-71, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 1003)
  - Hamlin, Edith, 1962-63 (Box 44, Folder 1004)
  - Harmsen, W. D., 1967 (Box 44, Folder 1005)
  - Harper, J. Russell, 1963-73 (Box 44, Folder 1006)
    See also: National Gallery of Canada, box 47, folder 1191
  - Harrell, Ida, 1962-64, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 1007)
  - Harrison, Michael, 1965-77 (Box 44, Folder 1008-1010)
  - Hart, Clare B., 1963-65 (Box 44, Folder 1011)
  - Harvey, Reginald Llewellyn, 1964 (Box 44, Folder 1012)
  - Hassrick, Peter, 1969-77, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 1013)
    See also: Amon Carter Museum, box 39, folders 704-712
  - Hayes, Edmund, 1963 (Box 44, Folder 1014)
  - Hayes, May, 1962-63 (Box 44, Folder 1015)
  - Haynes, Isabel M., 1962-63 (Box 44, Folder 1016)
  - Heaney, Charles, 1962-63 (Box 44, Folder 1017)
  - Hearthside Antiques, 1960-66 (Box 44, Folder 1018)
  - Helms, Margaret Neill, 1961-64 (Box 44, Folder 1019)
  - Hencke, Paul, 1965-66 (Box 44, Folder 1020)
  - Henderson, Eric, 1964 (Box 44, Folder 1021)
  - Henderson, Marlene; Henderson, W. W., 1967-68 (Box 44, Folder 1022)
  - Henry Gallery, 1963-69 (Box 44, Folder 1023)
  - Heuston, Enid Ingersoll, 1964, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 1024)
  - Hill, Romayne B., 1964 (Box 44, Folder 1025)
  - Hines, Felrath, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 1026)
  - Hirschl & Adler Galleries, 1963-75 (Box 44, Folder 1027)
  - Hitchman, Robert, 1959-76 (Box 44, Folder 1028)
  - Hoag, Betty Lochrie, 1962-72 (Box 44, Folder 1029)
  - Hoffman, Frank, Mr. and Mrs., 1963 (Box 44, Folder 1030)
  - Hogarth, Paul, 1967-72 (Box 44, Folder 1031)
  - Holmes, William H., 1964-65 (Box 44, Folder 1032)
  - Horsky, Emery, 1964 (Box 44, Folder 1033)
  - Hough, Helen C., 1963-64 (Box 44, Folder 1034)
  - Howe, Margery, 1960 Jun (Box 44, Folder 1035)
  - Howell, Warren
    See: John Howell Books, box 45, folders 1055-1057
  - Hudson's Bay Company, 1958-65 (Box 44, Folder 1036)
  - Huntington, Gloria F., 1964-72 (Box 44, Folder 1037)
  - Huss, John W., Mrs., 1963-65 (Box 44, Folder 1038)
  - "I" general, 1961-76 (Box 44, Folder 1039-1040)
  - Idaho Department of Health, 1963 (Box 44, Folder 1041)
  - Idaho Historical Society, 1963-73 (Box 44, Folder 1042)
  - Illinois Department of Public Health, 1963-65 (Box 44, Folder 1043)
  - International Business Machines Corporation, 1965 Jul (Box 44, Folder 1044)
  - International Institute for Conservation of Historical and Artistic Works, 1964-67 (Box 44, Folder 1045)
  - Irwin, Rea, 1963-64 (Box 44, Folder 1046)
  - Isaacs, Walter F., 1963-64 (Box 44, Folder 1047)
  - "J" general, 1961-73, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 1048-1049)
  - J. N. Bartfield Fine Book Studio, 1961-73 (Box 45, Folder 1050)
  - Jacksonville Museum, 1959-68 (Box 45, Folder 1051)
  - Janson, H. W., 1968 (Box 45, Folder 1052)
  - Jefferson County Historical Society, 1964-71 (Box 45, Folder 1053)
  - Jemne, Elsa, 1964-65 (Box 45, Folder 1054)
  - John Howell Books, 1959-76 (Box 45, Folder 1055-1057)
  - Johnson, William R., Mrs., 1963-64 (Box 45, Folder 1058)
  - Jones, Glen, Mrs., 1962-63 (Box 45, Folder 1059)
  - Jones, Nancy; Jones, Roy Farrington, 1972-74 (Box 45, Folder 1060)
  - Jorgenson, Virgil, 1964 (Box 45, Folder 1061)
  - Joslyn Art Museum, 1961-68 (Box 45, Folder 1062)
  - "K" general, 1959-81 (Box 45, Folder 1063-1065)
  - Kane, James, 1963-65 (Box 45, Folder 1066)
  - Kasper, Jack A.; Kasper, Ruth E., 1960-63, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 1067)
  - Keck, Caroline K., 1965 (Box 45, Folder 1068)
  - Kegg, Mabel, 1963-64 (Box 45, Folder 1069)
  - Keithley, Genevieve, 1963-66 (Box 45, Folder 1070)
  - Kemble, John H., 1961 (Box 45, Folder 1071)
  - Kennedy Galleries, 1957-75 (Box 45, Folder 1072-1073)
  - Kennedy, Michael